[
{
"id":"1",
"question":"Anyone who was shocked by the atrocities ought to ask himself what _____ to prevent them.",
"answer":"they could have done",
"opt1":"had they done",
"opt2":"they must have done",
"opt3":"they could have done",
"opt4":"did they do"
},
{
"id":"2",
"question":"_____ a large number of people in my life who have always done their utmost to help me achieve my goals.",
"answer":"There have been",
"opt1":"There were",
"opt2":"They were",
"opt3":"They have been",
"opt4":"There have been"
},
{
"id":"3",
"question":"I don't dislike the building. Now as _____ the neighbourhood, I do have concerns.",
"answer":"regards",
"opt1":"about",
"opt2":"well",
"opt3":"regards",
"opt4":"in"
},
{
"id":"4",
"question":"First, add some _____ chopped garlic to the tomatoes.",
"answer":"finely",
"opt1":"small",
"opt2":"finely",
"opt3":"tinily",
"opt4":"neatly"
},
{
"id":"5",
"question":"Due to lacking _____ , we couldn't open the new store as scheduled.",
"answer":"funds",
"opt1":"interest rates",
"opt2":"expenses",
"opt3":"shares",
"opt4":"funds"
},
{
"id":"6",
"question":"My sister ____ bought a laptop for her birthday last year.",
"answer":"was",
"opt1":"were",
"opt2":"was",
"opt3":"has",
"opt4":"had"
},
{
"id":"7",
"question":"There was ______ anger in his voice that I had to hang up.",
"answer":"so much",
"opt1":"as much",
"opt2":"such lot of",
"opt3":"such much",
"opt4":"so much"
},
{
"id":"8",
"question":"Why on earth ____ have done such a thing?",
"answer":"would you",
"opt1":"you",
"opt2":"you would",
"opt3":"would you",
"opt4":"if you"
},
{
"id":"9",
"question":"It seemed ____ been snowing, but we knew it was only some white dust that had covered the whole town.",
"answer":"as if it had",
"opt1":"like it has",
"opt2":"if it had",
"opt3":"as it had",
"opt4":"as if it had"
},
{
"id":"10",
"question":"Thanks for having me! I've had _____ with you guys.",
"answer":"such fun",
"opt1":"so fun",
"opt2":"such fun",
"opt3":"good time",
"opt4":"so good time"
}
]